Okay. Puppies.
Where do you stand on puppies?
(Bernadette:)A puppy once bit my face.
(Howard:)Of course it did.
(Leonard:)-How about that? Einstein was wrong.
-What?
(Leonard:)Approaching the speed of light doesn't
slow down time, approaching them does.
[MUSICAL RINGTONE PLAYING]
(Howard(phone rings):)Excuse me.
(Howard(phone rings):)Oh, damn. It's my mother.
(Bernadette:)-Are you going to answer it?
-I'm torn.
(Howard:)She might be dying and, you know,
wouldn't want to miss that.
On other hand, if let it go to voicemail,
I could play it over and over.
(Bernadette:)I know how you feel.
My mother makes me crazy.
Yeah, not as crazy
as my mother makes me.
(Bernadette:)Yeah? Does your mother call you
every day at work...
(Bernadette:)...to see if you've had a healthy lunch?
(Howard:)My mother calls me at work to see
if I had a healthy bowel movement.
Okay, does she lay out your clothes
for you in the morning...